United World Federalists mss. III, 1988-2013 LMC 2800
Lilly Library
United World Federalists mss. III
1988-2013
Lilly Library
United World Federalists
LMC 2800
1 Box
The United World Federalists mss. III, 1989-2013, consist of copies of United World.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift: 2012, 2013
Historical Note
United World is a small bi-monthly journal devoted to the issue of Democratic World Government (DWG). The journal has been published continuously since 1988.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of a nearly complete run of the journal United World.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged chronologically
Related Materials
See United World Federalists mss., United World Federalists mss. II, United World Federalists mss. IV, and United World Federalists mss. V, also located at the Lilly Library, Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana.
International relations; United States—Politics and government—20th century
- United World Periodical (Box 1)
  - The View From Space (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 2007 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 2009 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 2011 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2012 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 15th Anniversary Issue, 1988-2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 20th Anniversary Issue, 1988-2008 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- World Government Organization Coalition (Box 1)
  - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Rock (Box 1, Folder 30)